[
	{
		"question": "Who was the Last Great Viking Leader?",
		"options": [
			"Ragnar Lothbrok",
			"Harald Hardrada",
			"Erik the Red",
			"Leif Eriksson"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the oldest known monumental sculpture in Egypt?",
		"options": [
			"Pyramids of Giza",
			"Stonehenge",
			"The Sphinx",
			"Colosseum"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "When was the Iron Age period?",
		"options": [
			"Between 3000 BC and 2000 BC",
			"Between 1200 BC and 600 BC",
			"Between 300 BC and 1000 AD",
			"Between 1400 AD and 1600 AD"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What was the era of dinosaurs called?",
		"options": [
			"Mesozoic",
			"Cenozoic",
			"Paleozoic",
			"Precambrian"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "When did salem witch trials begin?",
		"options": [
			"May 1491",
			"January 1513",
			"February 1692",
			"March 1759"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "When was the Battle of Waterloo fought?",
		"options": [
            "21 September 1785",
			"18 June 1815",
			"30 January 1825",
			"5 July 1875"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Which was the shortest war in the history?",
		"options": [
			"Reconquista",
			"Anglo-Zanzibar",
			"Anglo-French Wars",
			"Battle of the Blackwater"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What do you call people who study fossils?",
		"options": [
			"Limnologist",
			"Seismologist",
			"Embalmer",
			"Paleontologist"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "When was the Leaning Tower of Pisa finished?",
		"options": [
			"1372",
			"1419",
			"1453",
			"1521"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "When was Adolf Hitler born?",
		"options": [
			"20 April 1889",
			"27 April 1889",
			"25 December 1889",
			"31 December 1889"
		],
		"answer": 0
	}
]